<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<catalog>
   <feedback id="review1">
      <message>Simply amazing. The amount of voice recognition is out of the world in EarTalk.
                 sometimes it feels like you?re talking to a human. 
                 It understands you in background noise too. Songs, when played, 
                 are accompanied with lyrics, 
                which makes it a good song along experience. Love this device</message>
      <name>Christine Berkley</name>
   </feedback>
   <feedback id="review2">
      <message>Loved this device. Was looking for something similar
                , and I found in TalkToMe Echo.I gifted the TalkToMe Echo 
                8 to my brother on his 50th Birthday and bought TalkToMe Echo
                 5 for myself.The best part of Echo Show is 
                 it versatility and multiple functions 
                 it can perform and the size is so apt.
                 Definitely recommend TalkToMee Echo to all.</message>
      <name>David Byer</name>
   </feedback>
   <feedback id="review3">
      <message>Why would you need a voice command light? 
      The same reason you need Google, Alexis, YouTube. 
      They just make life easier. Love that it not
       only says I'm here. It also tells you the brightness
        level you're on. It automatically turns off or @ your
         command. Keeps you from pressing the brightness
          button rather than on off switch. </message>
      <name>John Anthony</name>
   </feedback>
   <feedback id="review4">
      <message>Great light for my daughters room! 
      Clips to her bed and has the voice control 
      as well as a timer to automatically turn off! Great 
      brightness levels and color temperatures! Perfect for 
      our needs!</message>
      <name>Mrs. Sarah Buck</name>
   </feedback>
   <feedback id="review5">
      <message>My husband needed a new hands free unit so 
      purchased this one. After a couple of days he said he 
      wished the ear piece was smaller. I sent a note to service on 
      a Saturday night, by the next morning (Sunday!) I 
      received an answer. They told me they would send out a 
      small ear piece and it should take 5-7 days. It arrived in 3! I 
      received emails when it was shipped and again when it should be 
      delivered. GREAT service...oh..and he loves 
      the unit. Thanks Service Department.</message>
      <name>Dianne</name>
   </feedback>
   <feedback id="review6">
      <message>I'm a truck driver and we unload our own 
      trailers...it's imperative we use headsets that cancel 
      out the noise we make using roll up doors, electric dock plates and 
      power jacks. According to co-workers, THIS headset 
      works great! A few asked me to send them the info to order one 
      for themselves. Not only is it a great price but the battery 
      life is good (we spend 90% of our 14 hr days on the ph), it's e
      xtremely comfortable wear and it's secured on the ear 
      (can wear on either ear)</message>
      <name>Matthew</name>
   </feedback>
</catalog>